A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources, 1992-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series VII. Legislative Initiatives, 2002-2005., Extent: 4.2 cu. ft. (Box 108-119.)
  - 2005 General Assembly.
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 14)
- Series VIII. Public Relations Files, 2001-2005., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (Box 120-128.)
  Contains three types of public relations material including event files, photographs and speeches from the Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources. The activities and visits files (event files) contain correspondence, newspaper clippings, and other working papers related to particular Natural Resources-related events and issues. The photograph files contain photographs of selected events, as well as limited correspondence and other material. Also included are photographs of Governor Warner's cabinet and portraits of the Secretary and Deputy Secretary. The speech files are the most numerous in number, each representing a particular event during which the Secretary or Deputy Secretary spoke. Most of the files include multiple transcripts of the speech or remarks given, as well as other working papers associated with the event.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of file, then chronologically within. The photographs are arranged strictly alphabetically by subject, with no chronological order. (Accessions 42294 and 42398).
  - Activities and Visits.
    - Banners / Flags (miscellaneous), undated. (Box 1)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), 2002. (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), 2002. (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Goals and Initiatives, undated. (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Articles, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Articles, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Articles, 2005-2005. (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Articles (Prepared by SNR), 2002-2005. (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Northumberland Elementary Student Drawings, undated. (Box 2)
    - Piedmont Environmental Council Tour of Northern Virginia Development Patterns and Briefing Book, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Piedmont Environmental Council Tour of Northern Virginia Development Patterns and Briefing Book, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Piedmont Environmental Council Tour of Northern Virginia Development Patterns and Briefing Book, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Piedmont Environmental Council Tour of Northern Virginia Development Patterns and Briefing Book, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Piedmont Environmental Council Tour of Northern Virginia Development Patterns and Briefing Book, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Piedmont Environmental Council Tour of Northern Virginia Development Patterns and Briefing Book, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Piedmont Environmental Council Tour of Northern Virginia Development Patterns and Briefing Book, 2002. (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Timberlake Dam Scrapbook, 2005. (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Timberlake Dam Scrapbook, 2005. (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Photographs.
    - Basin Grand Winner Ceremony, 2001. (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Elizabeth River Project Omega Protein Donation, 2002. (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Cabinet, undated. (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 2003. (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, Secretary William T. (Portrait), 2002. (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Secretary William T. (Miscellaneous), undated. (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Paylor, Deputy Secretary David (Portrait), undated. (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Richmond County Simonson Public Boat Ramp, 2003. (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Secretary Murphy with First Lady Lisa Collis, undated. (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Secretary Murphy with Governor Warner (Group Photographs), undated. (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Secretary Murphy with Governor Warner (Speaking Engagements), undated. (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Warner, Governor Mark R. (Portrait), 2002. (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Speeches.
    - 2002.
      - Quotations for Speeches, 2002. (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - Senate Finance Commmittee, Natural Resources Subcommittee, 2002 January 23. (Box 121, Folder 14)
      - Association of Planning District Commissions, 2002 February 13. (Box 121, Folder 15)
      - Clean Water / Bay Friendly Farm Awards, 2002 February 18. (Box 121, Folder 16)
      - Virginia Rural Water Association, 2002 March 19. (Box 121, Folder 17)
      - Friends of the Shenandoah River Annual Membership and Awards Banquet, 2002 April 6. (Box 121, Folder 18)
      - Fluvanna Heritage Forum, 2002 April 6. (Box 121, Folder 19)
      - Environment Virginia, 2002 April 9-11. (Box 121, Folder 20)
      - Environment Virginia, 2002 April 9-11. (Box 121, Folder 21)
      - Environment Virginia, 2002 April 9-11. (Box 121, Folder 22)
      - Rotary Club of Norfolk, 2002 April 13. (Box 121, Folder 23)
      - Rotary Club of Norfolk, 2002 April 13. (Box 121, Folder 24)
      - Brown and Williamson E-3 Designation Ceremony, 2002 April 19. (Box 121, Folder 25)
      - Virginia Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts, Area I., 2002 April 26. (Box 121, Folder 26)
      - Virginia Conservation Network, 2002 April 27. (Box 121, Folder 27)
      - Nature Conservancy Annual Meeting, 2002 May 3. (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Rocketts Landing Launch, 2002 May 8. (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Virginia Tech Department of Geological Science Commencement, 2002 May 11. (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Department Technical Assistance Workshop and Locality Showcase, 2002 May 15. (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Department Technical Assistance Workshop and Locality Showcase, 2002 May 15. (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Manufacturers Association, Environmental Affairs Committee, 2002 May 16. (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Kauffman Aquaculture Center Groundbreaking Ceremony, 2002 May 17. (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Falls of the James Scenic River Advisory Board 30th Anniversary, 2002 May 20. (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Bar Association CLE Presentation, 2002 June 14. (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Water Quality Monitoring Celebration, 2002 June 21. (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - Thomas C. Sorensen Institute for Political Leadership, 2002 August 9. (Box 122, Folder 11)
      - Thomas C. Sorensen Institute for Political Leadership, 2002 August 9. (Box 122, Folder 12)
      - James Vincent Morgan Bridge Dedication, 2002 September 7. (Box 122, Folder 13)
      - Water Jam, Water Environment Association / American Waterworks Association, 2002 September 12. (Box 122, Folder 14)
      - Virginia 2020, 2002 September 13. (Box 122, Folder 15)
      - Prevention Alliance Conference, 2002 September 23. (Box 122, Folder 16)
      - Hampton Roads Sanitation, York River Treatment Plant, 2002 September 24. (Box 122, Folder 17)
      - Northern Virginia Transportation Referendum Debate, 2002 October 10. (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - Northern Virginia Transportation Referendum Debate, 2002 October 10. (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - Taste of the Chesapeake, Alliance for the Chesapeake Bay, 2002 October 12. (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - Bond Referenda, 2002. (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - Bond Referenda, 2002. (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - Bond Referenda, 2002. (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - Bond Referenda, 2002. (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - Bond Referenda, 2002. (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - National Water Monitoring Day, 2002 October 18. (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - Science in the Environment, 2002 November 9. (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - Southwestern Virginia Trip, 2002 October 20-23. (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - Southwestern Virginia Trip, 2002 October 20-23. (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - Southwestern Virginia Trip, 2002 October 20-23. (Box 123, Folder 13)
      - Water Resources Research Center Research Symposium, 2002 November 6. (Box 123, Folder 14)
      - Regent University Public Interest Legal Advocates, 2002 November 11. (Box 123, Folder 15)
      - Businesses for the Bay and Zero Release Conference, 2002 November 12. (Box 123, Folder 16)
      - Shared Potomac Strategy Conference, 2002 November 20. (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - Living Within Nature, 2002 November 21. (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - Infineon E-3 Event, 2002 December 19. (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - 2003.
      - Virginia Resource Use Education Council, 2003 January 7. (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Senate Finance Subcommittee on Economic Development and Natural Resources, 2003 January 8. (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - National Defense Industrial Association Symposium and Exhibition, 2003 April 8. (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - National Defense Industrial Association Symposium and Exhibition, 2003 April 8. (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - Citizens for a Better Eastern Shore, 2003 April 9. (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - International Watershed Management Symposium, 2003 April 19. (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - Simonson Public Boat Ramp Landing Dedication, 2003 April 21. (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - Coastal Nonpoint Implementation Meeting, 2003 April 29. (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - Environment Virginia, 2003 April 29 - May 1. (Box 124, Folder 12)
      - Environment Virginia, 2003 April 29 - May 1. (Box 124, Folder 13)
      - World Affairs Council, 2003 May 15. (Box 124, Folder 14)
      - New River Land Trust Seminar, 2003 May 21. (Box 124, Folder 15)
      - New River Land Trust Seminar, 2003 May 21. (Box 124, Folder 16)
      - New River Land Trust Seminar, 2003 May 21. (Box 124, Folder 17)
      - Chesapeake Bay Water Quality Briefing, 2003 May 28. (Box 124, Folder 18)
      - Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003 June 19. (Box 124, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Manufacturers Association Conference, 2003 September 9. (Box 124, Folder 20)
      - Virginia Manufacturers Association Conference, 2003 September 9. (Box 124, Folder 21)
      - Forestry and Wildlife Tour, Tidewater Resource Conservation and Development Council, 2003 October 16. (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - James River Association, Virginia Water Monitoring Day, 2003 October 17. (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Chesapeake Local Assistance Department Bay Act Workshop, 2003 October 21. (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Chesapeake Local Assistance Department Bay Act Workshop, 2003 October 21. (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 2003 October 23. (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Regional Water Resources Policy Committee, 2003 November 6. (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - Williamsburg Land Conservancy, 2003 November 19. (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - Outside the Beltway, IAC State Partnership Subcommittee Kick-Off Meeting, 2003 November 19. (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - HRSD Executive Committee, 2003 November 19. (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - Museum of Natural History Groundbreaking, 2003 December 2. (Box 125, Folder 10)
      - James River Partnership Meeting, 2003 December 3. (Box 125, Folder 11)
      - Virginia Coastal Program Workshop, 2003 December 4. (Box 125, Folder 12)
      - Virginia Coastal Program Workshop, 2003 December 4. (Box 125, Folder 13)
      - Virginia Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts Annual Meeting, 2003 December 8. (Box 125, Folder 14)
      - Roanoke Valley-Alleghany Regional Commission Annual Dinner, 2003 December 11. (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - 2004.
      - Presentation to the Senate Finance Committee, 2004 January 13. (Box 125, Folder 16)
      - Richmond Regional Planning District, 2004 February 12. (Box 125, Folder 17)
      - Virginia Chapter of The Wildlife Society, 2004 February 19. (Box 125, Folder 18)
      - Embrey Dam Breach, 2004 February 23. (Box 125, Folder 19)
      - Goshen Pass Dedication, 2004 March 30. (Box 125, Folder 20)
      - Environment Virginia, 2004 March 30-April 1. (Box 125, Folder 21)
      - Kauffman Aquaculture Center Dedication, 2004 April 13. (Box 125, Folder 22)
      - Southeastern Public Service Authority, Earth Day, 2004 April 22. (Box 125, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Main Street Communities, Manassas, 2004 May 3. (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - Capital to Capital Trail Kick-Off, 2004 May 15. (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - Chesapeake Bay Program Citizen's Advisory Committee, 2004 May 20-21. (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Symposium on Nuisance Wild Animal Management in Virginia, 2004 June 1. (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2004 June 29. (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Western Virginia Water Authority, Roanoke Inauguration Celebration, 2004 June 30. (Box 126, Folder 6)
      - St. Christopher's Summer Institute on Leadership and Public Service, 2004 July 9. (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - Piedmont Art's Association / Museum of Natural History, 2004 July 20. (Box 126, Folder 8)
      - Local Government Officials Conference, 2004 August 2. (Box 126, Folder 9)
      - Testimony, House Committee on Government Reform, 2004 August 20. (Box 126, Folder 10)
      - Rotary Club, Fairfax, 2004 September 13. (Box 126, Folder 11)
      - EPA State Secretaries Meeting, 2004 September 14-15. (Box 126, Folder 12)
      - EPA State Secretaries Meeting, 2004 September 14-15. (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - Virginia Hospitals for a Healthy Environment, 2004 September 16. (Box 126, Folder 14)
      - Potomac River Fisheries Commission, 2004 September 17. (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - Environmental Excellence Awards, 2004 September 21-22. (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - Northern Virginia Conservation Trust, 2004 September 24. (Box 126, Folder 17)
      - Senate Committee on Agriculture, Conservation and Natural Resources, 2004 September 28. (Box 126, Folder 18)
      - Virginia Birding and Wildlife Trail, Piedmont Dedication, 2004 September 30. (Box 126, Folder 19)
      - Jamestown 2007 Steering Committee, 2004 October 6. (Box 126, Folder 20)
      - Northern Neck Regional Litter Summit, 2004 October 13. (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - Menokin, 2004 October 17. (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Brownsfield Conference, 2004 October 21. (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Brownsfield Conference, 2004 October 21. (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - High Bridge Train Ride, 2004 October 26. (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Executive Institute, 2004 October 27. (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission Regarding Nutrient Management, 2004 November 8. (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - Institute for Environmental Negotiation Symposium, 2004 November 18-19. (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - 2005.
      - Virginia Association of Planning District Commissions Winter Conference, 2005 January 18. (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - APVA Legislative Day, 2005 January 18. (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - British Embassy, 2005 February 24. (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - Virginia Association of Wetland Professionals, 2005 March 4. (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - Bill Signing Ceremony, 2005 March 24. (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - Thomas Jefferson Institute Conference, 2005 April 6. (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - Arbor Day, 2005 April 8. (Box 127, Folder 15)
      - Environment Virginia, 2005 April 11. (Box 127, Folder 16)
      - Environment Virginia, 2005 April 11. (Box 127, Folder 17)
      - Environment Virginia, 2005 April 11. (Box 127, Folder 18)
      - Environment Virginia, 2005 April 11. (Box 127, Folder 19)
      - Walnut Valley Farm Dedication, 2005 April 17. (Box 127, Folder 20)
      - Northeastern Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies Annual Conference, 2005 April 18. (Box 127, Folder 21)
      - Lincoln Prize, 2005 April 21. (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Waste Solutions Forum, 2005 April 28. (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Waste Solutions Forum, 2005 April 28. (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Governor's Conference on Greenways, Blueways and Trails, 2005 May 2. (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Smithfield Foods E-3 Awards, 2005 May 3. (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Clean Commute Day, 2005 May 6. (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Citizen's Advisory Committee, 2005 May 19. (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Interstate Air Quality Council, 2005 May 20. (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - York River Pier Dedication, 2005 June 15. (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - York River Pier Dedication, 2005 June 15. (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Horseshoe Bend Boat Access Dedication, 2005 July 7. (Box 128, Folder 11)
      - Land Conservation Speech, Senate Finance Subcommittee on Economic Development and Natural Resources, 2005 July 11. (Box 128, Folder 12)
      - E-4 Designation Ceremony, Lockheed Martin, 2005 August 11. (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - Elizabeth River Leadership Summit, 2005 August 19. (Box 128, Folder 14)
      - Elizabeth River Leadership Summit, 2005 August 19. (Box 128, Folder 15)
      - Environmental Education Conference, 2005 September 7. (Box 128, Folder 16)
      - Captain John Smith Water Trails Briefing / National Greenways Award, 2005 September 8. (Box 128, Folder 17)
      - Alliance for the Chesapeake Bay / SunTrust Green Roof Program, 2005 September 13. (Box 128, Folder 18)
      - Virginia's Sustainable Future Summit, 2005 September 14. (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Virginia's Sustainable Future Summit, 2005 September 14. (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - St. John's Church Foundation Visitor's Center Opening, 2005 September 22. (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Northeast CZM Partners Workshop, 2005 October 5. (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Northeast CZM Partners Workshop, 2005 October 5. (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - National Water Research Symposium, 2005 October 11. (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - National Water Research Symposium, 2005 October 11. (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - Environmental Law Forum, 2005 October 13. (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Keep Virginia Beautiful Awards, 2005 October 19. (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - Seven Bends State Park Dedication, 2005 October 24. (Box 129, Folder 10)
      - Division of Chesapeake Bay Local Assistance Annual Workshop, 2005 November 3. (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - Launch of the John Smith Shallop, 2005 November 4. (Box 129, Folder 12)
      - Virginia Stream Alliance, 2005 November 15. (Box 129, Folder 13)
      - Symposium on the Church and Virginia's Tribes, 2005 November 17. (Box 129, Folder 14)
      - Governor's Chesapeake Bay Press Conference, 2005 November 21. (Box 129, Folder 15)
      - Virginia Association of Soil and Water Conservation Districts, 2005 December 5. (Box 129, Folder 16)
      - Lunch with Leaders, 2005 Decemer 5. (Box 129, Folder 17)
      - Governor's Budget Press Conference on Water Quality Funding, 2005 December 13. (Box 129, Folder 18)
- Series IX. Special Program Files, 1999-2005., Extent: 1.75 cu. ft. (Box 130-134.)
  Contains files pertaining to specific organizations and issues related to Virginia's natural resources, such as the Governor's Leadership Summit and Partnership, the Statewide Agencies Radar System (STARS), and the King William Reservoir. Researchers should note that the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation folders also contain information on the Jamestown 2007 Steering Committee. The folders devoted to the King William Reservoir, the Ghost Fleet and Occoneechee State Park are comprised mostly of constituent correspondence. (Accession 42294).
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Funding Commission, 2003. (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Funding Commission, 2003. (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Funding Commission, 2003. (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Funding Commission, 2003. (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Funding Commission, 2003. (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Funding Commission, 2003. (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Funding Commission, 2003. (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Future of Virginia's Environment Joint Subcommittee Study, 2002. (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Ghost Fleet, 2002. (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Ghost Fleet, 2002. (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Ghost Fleet, 2002. (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Leadership Summit, 2003. (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Partnership, 2004. (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Partnership, 2004. (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Governor's Natural Resources Partnership, 2004. (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Historic Jamestown Planning Committee, 2004. (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Jamestown 2007 Steering Committee, 2003-2005. (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1999-2005. (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1999-2005. (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1999-2005. (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1999-2005. (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1999-2005. (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1999-2005. (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1999-2005. (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - King William Reservoir, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Occoneechee State Park Golf Course, 2002. (Box 134, Folder 6)